Tony Schwartz Collection
Motion Picture, Broadcasting and Recorded Sound Division, Library of Congress
- Series 3. Works and Publications, 1950–2004, 5 linear feet
  - Writings, 1953–2004, undated
    - "Do You Really Have a Library?" 1959-04 (Box-folder 157/17)
      Article from Hi-Fi Tape Recording.
    - "Electronic Campaigning" draft, undated (Box-folder 157/18)
      Fifty-two pages.
    - "The Electronic Museum and Information Distribution" draft and research materials, circa 1953–circa 1967 (Box-folder 157/19)
      Research, transcripts of interviews, and a draft of the article.
    - Environmental Media draft and stationery, undated (Box-folder 157/20)
    - "Ethics in Political Media Communication," 1980-01-14–1980-02-28 (Box-folder 157/21)
      Correspondence, article draft, and copyright agreement.
    - "The Exhibition of Sound," undated (Box-folder 157/22)
      Article from an unknown magazine.
    - "The Future Is Now" drafts, 1983 (Box-folder 157/23)
    - Guide for Tape Recording draft and correspondence, 1962-03-28–circa 1963 (Box-folder 157/24)
      Drafts of a tape recording guide by Tony Schwartz and letters from Art Direction, the magazine of creative advertising.
      See also "Sound Directions" column.
    - "Hearing's Believing?" 1967-03 (Box-folder 157/25)
      Unknown publisher.
    - "How to Change an Image" draft, undated (Box-folder 157/26)
      Article draft. Unknown publisher.
    - "How to Grow Grass-Roots in the Global Village" brochures, contracts, and correspondence, 1969–1987-03-05 (Box-folder 157/27)
      See also Project 86.
    - "How to Use Radio Advertising Most Effectively," 1979-10-15 (Box-folder 157/28)
      Article from Boardroom Reports.
      See also Boardroom Reports in commercial client files.
    - "How to Watch Debates Today" draft, 1991-02-26 (Box-folder 157/29)
    - "How TV Will Change Government," 1978-02-05 (Box-folder 157/30)
      Article from the Daily News.
    - "The Inside of the Outside," 1972-01 (Box-folder 157/31)
      Article from Politeia magazine, volume 1, number 3.
    - "Kids and Cats" transcript, undated (Box-folder 157/32)
      Transcript from interviews with principals.
    - Correspondence relating to "The Language: Thinking, Writing, Communicating," 1980-05-27–1981-01-19 (Box-folder 157/33)
      Correspondence from Maryland Center for Public Broadcasting.
    - "Let's Not Make a Fatal Mistake" column drafts, 1983-03-02–circa 1983 (Box-folder 157/34)
      Drafts for a column about instant hesitation in Electronics Magazine and correspondence.
    - Letters to the editor, undated (Box-folder 157/35)
      Titles: "Earsight," (New York Times), "Principle or Principal?," (Advertising Age).
    - “Listen”, 1978-05-05–1979-03-20 (Box-folder 157/36)
      Original article, reprints from TV Guide, and letters from readers.
    - "Mass Communication," 1979-07-11–1980-10 (Box-folder 157/37)
      Article for the American Encyclopedia. Master copy.
    - "The Meaning of Video Replay," 1985-01-11 (Box-folder 157/38)
      Correspondence with Video Review and article.
    - Media Industry Newsletter, 1967–2004
      Acronym: MIN.
      See also Media the Second God.
      - Research, correspondence relating to USPS column, 1978-12-20–1984-12-09 (Box-folder 158/1)
      - Correspondence, 1980-03-06–2004-07-12 (Box-folder 158/2)
        Some newsletters attached to correspondence.
      - Research, 1980-04-28–1984-04-09 (Box-folder 158/3)
      - Newsletters, 1984-05-16–1998-03-30 (Box-folder 158/4)
        Draft for Planned Reactions, Inc.
      - Drafts, 1985-08-27–1986-04-10 (Box-folder 158/5)
        Some undated article drafts, Planned Reactions, Inc.
      - Drafts, 1989-01-03–1989-12-18 (Box-folder 158/6)
      - Columns, 1976-06-14–1983-08-10 (Box-folder 158/7)
        Photocopies of columns. Original folder titles were "Radio has yet to be discovered" and "On target."
        Pages numbered chronologically by date.
      - "Uses and Misuses of Advertising" columns, 1975-12-19–1982-03-17 (Box-folder 158/8)
      - Column compilation booklet, 1977 (Box-folder 158/9)
        Fifty-four page booklet, with an index of Schwartz's MIN columns from before 1977.
      - "Social Effects of Media" columns, 1979-03-19–1983-08-24 (Box-folder 158/10)
      - "Political Airwaves" columns, 1976-07-19–1983-05-18 (Box-folder 158/11)
      - "And Now the News!" columns, 1967-04–1982-10-20 (Box-folder 158/12)
      - "Researching the Consumer" columns, 1975-11-14–1982-03-03 (Box-folder 159/1)
      - "Shoes and Ships and Sealing Wax" columns, 1968-01–1983-11-16 (Box-folder 159/2)
      - "Recording" columns, 1963-10–1980-07-23 (Box-folder 159/3)
        Also includes "Sound for Photographers" and "Tony Schwartz on Sound" columns.
      - "Media and Education" columns, 1967-07–1982-05-05, undated (Box-folder 159/4)
        Pages numbered chronologically by date: added newsletter, 1977-02-21.
      - Columns, 1967-03–1993-04-26, undated (Box-folder 159/5)
        Mnemonic Speech cover and a compilation booklet of Tony Schwartz's MIN columns with index and introduction. Most drafts are undated.
      - Columns, undated (Box-folder 159/6)
      - "The FTC's Print and Buggy Romance with Truth," circa 1967 (Box-folder 159/7)
      - "Television and Violence" research and articles, 1969-11-15–1982-05-06 (Box-folder 159/8)
      - "Hear and There," 1992-10-26–1992-11-23 (Box-folder 159/9)
        Two columns.
      - Letter concerning a Tony Schwartz MIN column, 1977-08-30 (Box-folder 159/10)
        Letter from David Marsh at CBS regarding an interview Tony Schwartz wrote about in MIN; interview transcript included.
    - Media Lobbying flier, undated (Box-folder 159/11)
    - Media, the Second God, circa 1970s–circa 1990s
      - Post publication materials, 1982-07-16–1987 (Box-folder 159/12)
        Includes correspondence regarding the Japanese translation of the book.
      - Book notes, undated (Box-folder 159/13)
      - Artwork, circa 1980 (Box-folder 159/14)
        Artwork by Nurit Karlin.
      - Nurit Karlin Statue of Liberty artwork, circa 1980circa 1980 (Box-folder 230/9-10)
        Folder 9 contains a negative print of Karlin's drawing that has been pasted to a backing board, 12x22 inches. Folder 10 contains two paste-up copies of the drawing, one positive and one negative, each with a tissue overlay and each measuring 12x22 inches.
        Karlin's Statue of Liberty drawing faces p. [3] in the first edition of the book (1981).
      - Fan letters and reviews, 1981–1982 (Box-folder 160/1)
      - Publicity, 1981–1982 (Box-folder 160/2)
        Magazines, articles, correspondence, PR drafts, scripts, and invoices.
      - Cover art, first edition, 1981 (Box-folder 160/3)
        Correspondence, articles, and cover drafts.
      - Cover lettering and design, 1983 paperback edition, circa 1983 (Box-folder 226/6)
        Paste-up of the word "Media," 10 1/2x8 1/2 inches; negative image of the full cover, opened, printed on three-hole-punched plastic, 11x14 inches; and a positive paper print of the full cover, opened, 8x12 1/2 inches.
      - Cover lettering and design, 1983 paperback edition, circa 1983 (Box-folder 230/8)
        Four orange sheets of paper, each 12 1/2x16 inches and three-hole-punched, containing paste-up negatives of front and back cover lettering and a Tony Schwartz photograph, for the 1983 paperback edition.
      - Post publication, circa 1980s (Box-folder 160/4)
        Invoices, articles, correspondence, and PR.
      - John Jay campaign case study, 1981 (Box-folder 160/5)
        A photocopy of the chapter from the book.
      - Review correspondence, 1981–1983 (Box-folder 160/6)
      - Petrov interview, circa 1990s (Box-folder 160/7)
      - Book draft, circa 1980s (Box-folder 160/8-9)
      - Correspondence, circa 1980 (Box-folder 160/10)
        Correspondence and drafts. There is one 8x10-inch contact sheet of various photos of Tony Schwartz in his office.
      - Research, circa 1970s–circa 1980s (Box-folder 161/1-2)
        Magazines, articles, correspondence, drafts.
      - Correspondence, circa 1980 (Box-folder 161/3)
        Rights, colleague feedback.
      - Correspondence, 1985-05-01 (Box-folder 161/4)
      - Book, first edition, 1981 (Box-folder 161/5)
        Hardback with note cards inside.
      - Book draft and research, 1977-05-23–1980-02-20 (Box-folder 161/6)
        Correspondence and notes on the book draft and research materials. Includes copies of Media Industry Newsletter (MIN) column articles.
        See also Media Industry Newsletter.
      - The Second God: Media in the Post-Literate Society, undated (Box-folder 161/7)
        A draft of the book with one page of notes to accompany the tabs marked throughout the draft.
    - "The Microphone as a Lens," undated (Box-folder 161/8)
      Article from the magazine Popular Photography.
    - Letter regarding The Naked Computer, 1983-01-05 (Box-folder 161/9)
      Letter regarding an article Schwartz was writing for the book.
    - "Narrowcasting: Tune In Your Listeners with Radio," 1980-02-09 (Box-folder 161/10)
      Letter of agreement.
    - "New Voices" column, 1969-01–1969-11 (Box-folder 161/11)
      Educational Television magazines and correspondence.
    - "Nynex Impact" biography draft and article, undated (Box-folder 161/12)
      Draft of a biography and article on the impact of the telephone in Schwartz's life.
    - On Political Advertising brochure, undated (Box-folder 161/13)
      American Advertising Museum brochure.
    - "Perception or Dropouts?" 1968-04 (Box-folder 161/14)
      Music Notes magazine.
    - Popular Photography correspondence and articles, 1962-12-17–1965-05 (Box-folder 161/15)
    - "Puncturing Advertising Myths," 1977-06-30 (Box-folder 161/16)
    - Correspondence concerning "Radio: The Forgotten Medium," 1979-11-28–1979-12-17 (Box-folder 162/1)
      Correspondence for the magazine Campaigns and Elections.
    - "Radio: Two Creative Methods," 1978-05-29 (Box-folder 162/2)
      Advertising Age article.
    - "The RCA Tape Cartridge," 1959-04 (Box-folder 162/3)
      Modern Hi-Fi article, number 2.
    - The Responsive Chord, 1960s–1992
      - Chapter drafts, 1960s–1973 (Box-folder 162/4)
        Drafts of The Responsive Chord book chapters: "Introduction," "Sound in the Environment," "Education in the Global Village," "Political Communication, or, How to Package Voters," "Women's Discussion," and La Monte Young page "Dream Music."
      - Book draft, 1973 (Box-folder 162/5)
        Final print draft.
      - Correspondence, 1977-08-16–1992-02-11 (Box-folder 162/6)
        Reprint requests, Doubleday correspondence.
      - Master book draft, circa 1973 (Box-folder 162/7)
        Master print draft with corrections.
      - Publicity, circa 1973–circa 1975 (Box-folder 162/8)
      - Fan letters and other materials, 1973-11-08–1975-01-14 (Box-folder 162/9)
        Correspondence, reviews, PR drafts, radio publicity spot sales reports.
      - Publicity materials, 1957, circa 1971–circa 1980s, 2001 (Box-folder 162/10)
        Book cover designs, correspondence, reviews, publicity, radio spot invoices. Included are five photographs of Anton Schwartz for the book.
      - First edition office copy, 1973 (Box-folder 162/11)
        Personal office copy of the book with handwritten notes and tabs. The date “1978-09-24” is written on the dust jacket.
      - Paperback copy, 1974 (Box-folder 163/1)
      - "Hard Sell, Soft Sell, Deep Sell" and other materials, 1992 (Box-folder 163/2)
        Section of the book used in a communications reader for Simon Fraser University. Also contains a section of Marshal McLuhan's Understanding Media: The Extensions of Man and "Ads: Keeping Upset with the Joneses."
        See also the McLuhan correspondence file, McLuhan symposium content, and the extensive McLuhan subject files.
    - "Schwartz on Media," 1972-07 (Box-folder 163/3)
      Politea article, volume 1, number 4.
    - "60 Minutes" op-ed drafts, 1968–undated (Box-folder 163/4)
    - "Sound Directions," 1960s
      Art Direction magazine.
      - Column, circa 1960s (Box-folder 163/5-7)
        See also "Guide for Tape Recording."
    - Correspondence relating to "Speed Hearing: Variable Velocity Comprehension," 1971-04-20–1971-05-15 (Box-folder 163/8)
      Letters in response to article in BM/E magazine.
    - "Stimuli and Responses" handout, undated (Box-folder 163/9)
      A handout made by Schwartz referencing Erich Fromm's The Anatomy of Human Destructiveness.
    - "The Swinging Door to the Mind," undated (Box-folder 163/10)
      A column from an unknown publication. The column mentions Schwartz's theory on “earlids.”
    - "The Tape Around Us," 1974-08 (Box-folder 163/11)
      High Fidelity article by Tony Schwartz and John Carey.
    - "Task Oriented Paid Media to Affect Public Behavior" drafts, undated (Box-folder 163/12)
    - "The Terminology of Tony Schwartz," undated (Box-folder 163/13)
      Quick reference.
    - Drafts and original concept notes relating to "This Won't Take Long, Did It? A Prologue to the Polaroid Revolution," undated (Box-folder 163/14)
    - "Thoughts on Political Advertising," 1972-12 (Box-folder 163/15)
      CLIO article, co-author Michael Rowan.
    - "Tony Schwartz On" flier, undated (Box-folder 163/16)
      A one page flier containing remarks from Tony Schwartz on various media topics: radio, television, print, videocassettes, environmental media, and multimedia.
    - "To Replay Is to Know," undated (Box-folder 163/17)
      Article from Video Review.
    - "Toward Effective Advertising" draft, 1973 (Box-folder 163/18)
    - "TV... an Auditory Medium," 1979-02-24 (Box-folder 163/19)
      TV Guide article.
    - "Using Radio" drafts, undated (Box-folder 163/20)
    - "Using Today's Media to Change Behavior" draft, undated (Box-folder 163/21)
      Co-author John Carey.
    - Materials relating to "VCRs Turn Broadcasting into Narrowcasting," 1986-03–1986-04-04 (Box-folder 164/1)
      Drafts of article, correspondence with Video Magazine, and Esquire article "The ReDecade."
    - "Voice of the City," 1953-01-12–1996-09-02 (Box-folder 164/2)
      90.9 WBUR, Boston University Radio, Adventures in Music.
    - "What Does One of the Most Inventive Minds in Advertising Think about Research?" 1974-06 (Box-folder 164/3)
      Writer's Digest article.
    - Drafts and correspondence relating to "What Is a Negative Political Ad?" 1988-11-23 (Box-folder 164/4)
      Drafts and correspondence with New York Times for op-ed piece.
    - "What Really Matters, Searching for Wisdom in America," circa 1990s (Box-folder 164/5)
      Joke advertisement for a fake book by Schwartz.
    - "What's Water" drafts and research, 1973–1975 (Box-folder 164/6)
    - "When the Unreal Becomes Real" draft and research materials, circa 1973–undated (Box-folder 164/7)
- Series 4. Subject Files, 1912–2005, 15.2 linear feet
  Arranged in three groupings: General subject files, files on Marshall McLuhan, and files on smoking-related topics.
  - General subject files, 1912–2005
    Consists of published material, correspondence, and other material concerning people, organizations, and topics of interest to Tony Schwartz.
    Arranged alphabetically by name of individual, organization, and topic.
    - 1976 U.S. senatorial campaign research, circa 1976 (Box-folder 226/7)
    - 35 Plus Committee, circa 1980–1995 (Box-folder 165/1)
    - 35-64 Marketing, circa 1980–1989 (Box-folder 165/2)
    - ABC coverage of 1982 New York City marathon, 1982 (Box-folder 165/3)
    - Advertising agency executives' attitudes toward radio, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 165/4)
    - Advertising and marketing, circa 1912–1990 (Box-folder 165/5-8)
    - Advertising and marketing photocopies, 1978-05 (Box-folder 226/8)
      Oversized. Two articles: "Scoring a Perfect Pitch," by Joanne Kelleher, Ad East, May 1978, pages 22-23; and "Two Creative Methods, but Both Sell," Advertising Age, May 29, 1978, page R36.
    - African American topics, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 165/9)
    - Aging, circa 1990–1999 (Box-folder 165/10)
    - AIDS, circa 1980–2005 (Box-folder 166/1)
    - Roger Ailes, circa 1985–1995 (Box-folder 166/2)
    - Alcohol, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 166/3)
    - Alliance of the Building Community, circa 1990–2005 (Box-folder 166/4)
    - American Council on Science and Health, 1991 (Box-folder 166/5)
    - AMICUS, Inc., circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 166/6)
    - Animal rights, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 166/7)
    - Anthropology, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 166/8)
    - Anxiety Disorder Association of America, circa 1990–1999 (Box-folder 166/9)
    - Apartheid, circa 1980–2005 (Box-folder 166/10)
    - Architecture, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 166/11)
    - Reprint of article on Soviet architecture, 1942-11 (Box-folder 226/9)
      Reprint of "Soviet Architecture Today," by Edward Carter, from The Architectural Review, November 1942, pages 107-114.
    - Art, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 166/12)
    - Articles on individuals, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 166/13)
    - Articles that mention Tony Schwartz, circa 1950–2005 (Box-folder 166/14)
    - Moses Asch, 1971–2000 (Box-folder 167/1)
    - Astronomy and space, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 167/2)
    - Attitudes Towards a New Cassette Product, 1972-11 (Box-folder 167/3)
    - W.H. Auden, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 167/4)
    - Audio Engineering Society, 1966–1970 (Box-folder 167/5)
    - Audio recording and preservation, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 167/6)
    - Battleground, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 167/7)
    - Belafonte House, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 167/8)
    - Jack Bemporad, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 167/9)
    - Bettman Archive, 1988–1989 (Box-folder 167/10)
    - Joe Biden, circa 1970–1979 (Box-folder 167/11)
    - Book reviews, 1980–2000 (Box-folder 167/12-13)
    - Boys Choir of Harlem, 1988–1988 (Box-folder 167/14)
    - Oscar Brand, 1994 (Box-folder 167/15)
    - Will Burtin, circa 1977–1977 (Box-folder 167/16)
    - Anne Burton, 1986–1986 (Box-folder 167/17)
    - George H. W. Bush, 1980–2005 (Box-folder 167/18)
    - Business Enterprise Trust, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 167/19)
    - Business topics, 1990–1999 (Box-folder 167/20)
    - Earl Butz, 1973 (Box-folder 167/21)
    - Campaign Insider, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 167/22)
    - Capital Children's Museum, 1988–1988 (Box-folder 167/23)
    - Jean Carlu, circa 1940–2005 (Box-folder 168/1)
    - [Carpenter?] manuscript, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 168/2)
    - Edmund Carpenter, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 168/3)
    - Jimmy Carter, circa 1975–2005 (Box-folder 168/4)
      See also Jimmy Carter 1976 presidential election files and the Gerald Rafshoon subject file.
    - Censorship, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 168/5)
    - Center for Media and Values, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 168/6)
      The Center was later named Center for Media Literacy.
    - Marguerite Chandler oversample, 1990-01 (Box-folder 168/7)
    - Child development, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 168/8)
    - City University of New York (CUNY), 1990-11-09 (Box-folder 168/9)
    - Civil liberties organizations, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 168/10)
      Includes ACLU and National Emergency Civil Liberties Committee materials.
    - Civil rights, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 168/11)
    - Bill Clinton, circa 1990–2000 (Box-folder 168/12)
      See also files on Clinton's presidential campaign.
    - Clinton Urban Renewal Site, circa 1985–2005 (Box-folder 168/13)
    - Coliseum Apartments, 1983 (Box-folder 168/14)
    - Colleges and universities brochures, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 168/15)
    - Columbia Television, 1989-08 (Box-folder 168/16)
      Includes CTV proposal by Jack Limpert.
    - Communism, circa 1990–1999 (Box-folder 168/17)
    - Community policing, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 168/18)
    - Consumer product safety and consumer protection, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 168/19)
    - Contact sheets, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 168/20)
    - Copyright, circa 1980–2005 (Box-folder 168/21)
    - Crime and law enforcement, 1960–2000 (Box-folder 169/1-4)
    - Crimestoppers, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 169/5)
    - Crown Heights riot, 1991–2000 (Box-folder 169/6)
      Includes Schwartz interview with Norman Rosenbaum.
    - Current interests, opened 1989-10-03, 1988–1990 (Box-folder 169/7)
    - Current Interests, opened 1989-12, 1989-12–1990-05 (Box-folder 169/8)
    - Daily News strike, 1993–2000 (Box-folder 169/9)
    - National Center for Telephone Research printout relating to the Daily News, 1978-01 (Box-folder 227/1)
    - "Daisy ad" responses and related material, 1964–2005 (Box-folder 169/10)
    - Sister Camille D'Arienzo, circa 1991–2005 (Box-folder 169/11)
    - David Goldman Agency, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 170/1)
    - The Defense Monitor, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 170/2)
    - Ed Deming, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 170/3)
    - Democratic party, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 170/4)
    - David N. Dinkins, circa 1990–2000 (Box-folder 170/5)
    - Disabilities and impairments, circa 1970–2000 (Box-folder 170/6)
    - Dole Foundation, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 170/7)
    - Drug awareness and abuse, circa 1980–2000 (Box-folder 170/8-9)
    - Drunk driving, circa 1985–1990 (Box-folder 170/10)
    - Charles Eames, 1977–1977 (Box-folder 170/11)
    - Economy, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 170/12)
    - Thomas Edison, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 170/13)
    - Edna McConnell Clark Foundation, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 170/14)
    - Education and learning, circa 1960–2005, (1 folder) (Box 170-171, Box 170, Box 171)
    - Ronnie Eldridge, circa 1980–1999 (Box-folder 171/2)
    - Emerson College, 1983–2000 (Box-folder 171/3)
    - Employment topics, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 171/4)
    - Energy politics and issues, 1979 (Box-folder 171/5)
    - Morris Engel, circa 1990–1999 (Box-folder 171/6)
    - Entertainment, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 171/7)
    - Environmental awareness and activism, circa 1960–2000 (Box-folder 171/8)
    - Eve Epstein, 1998–2000 (Box-folder 171/9)
    - John Henry Faulk, 1985–1995 (Box-folder 171/10)
    - Federal Communications Commission, circa 1960–2000 (Box-folder 171/11)
    - Federal Elections Commission, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 171/12)
    - Federal Trade Commission, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 171/13)
    - Field Museum of Natural History, circa 1980–2005 (Box-folder 171/14)
    - Film strips, 1963–2000 (Box-folder 171/15)
    - First Tennessee Bank marketing research, 1977 (Box-folder 171/16-17)
    - Focus on Freedom, circa 1985–1989 (Box-folder 172/1)
    - Folklore and folk music, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 172/2)
    - Fonts, circa 1990–2000 (Box-folder 172/3)
    - Foreign language learning, circa 1990–2000 (Box-folder 172/4)
    - Forward Publishing Company, Inc., circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 172/5)
    - Foster Parents Plan, 1989 (Box-folder 172/6)
    - Stephen Foster, circa 1987–1987 (Box-folder 172/7)
    - Stephen O. Frankfurt, circa 1964–1964 (Box-folder 172/8)
    - Buckminster Fuller, circa 1971–2000 (Box-folder 172/9)
    - Garden Source Furnishings, 1992 (Box-folder 172/10)
    - David Garth, 1989–2000 (Box-folder 172/11)
    - Noel Gayler, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 172/12)
    - Newt Gingrich, 1995–1995 (Box-folder 172/13)
    - Rudolph Giuliani, circa 1980–2005 (Box-folder 172/14)
    - Gleitsman Foundation, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 172/15)
      See also Letter from Alan L. Gleitsman.
    - Globalism, circa 1970–2005 (Box-folder 172/16)
    - Erving Goffman, 1972–1972 (Box-folder 172/17)
    - Gerald Goldhaber, 1968–1980 (Box-folder 172/18)
    - Barry Goldwater, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 172/19)
    - Howard Luck Gossage, 1968 (Box-folder 172/20)
    - Edward M. Gottschall, 1969–1969 (Box-folder 172/21)
    - Graphic design magazines, 1962–1987 (Box-folder 173/1)